# Soheil Changizi

Computer Scientist

### Profile

Creative and self-motivated Computer Scientist interested in research and implementation. Adequate knowledge of programming languages and frameworks relevant for machine learning and full-stack web development. Committed to working as a team member and collaborating with others.

## Education

M.Sc. in Computer Science, University of Manitoba, Winnipeg 2021- Present

B.Sc. in Computer Engineering, K. N. Toosi University of Technology, Tehran 2015 - 2020

Last two years' GPA: 3.92/4.00 (18.20/20)

## Employment History

Teaching Assistant at University of Manitoba, Winnipeg 2021- Present

Backend Developer at Brilacasck, Tehran

2017 - 2020

Teaching Assistant at K. N. Toosi University of Technology, Tehran 2016 - 2020

Research Assistant at KN2C lab, Tehran 2017 - 2018

## Fields of Interest

Reinforcement Learning - Robotics - Computer Vision Quantum Computing - Web Development

## Courses

- Advanced Machine Learning, University of Manitoba
- CS Education Research & Edtech Innovations, University of Manitoba
- Deep Learning Specialization, DeepLearning.Al
- Reinforcement Learning Specialization, University of Alberta & Alberta Machine Intelligence Institute
- Foundation of Computer Vision, K. N. Toosi University of Technology

#### **Details**

Winnipeg Canada

soheilchangizi1997@gmail.com

#### Links

My Website Linkedin Github

#### **Skills**

Python

C++

Java

OpenCV Keras

PyTorch

Node.js

Express.js

Flask

**JavaScript** 

React

Material UI

MongoDB

MySQL

Git

Linux

#### Languages

English

Farsi

Arabic